Love hurts.
Strange Darling is a horror, thriller film directed by JT Mollner.
Nothing is what it seems when a twisted one-night stand spirals
into a serial killer’s vicious murder spree.
The Lady, played by Willa Fitzgerald.
The Demon, played by Kyle Gallner.
Gale, played by Madisen Beaty.
Tanya, played by Bianca A. Santos.
Pete, played by Steven Michael Quezada.
Frederick, played by Ed Begley Jr..
Strange Darling is a 2023 American psychological crime
thriller film written and directed by JT Mollner.
The film stars Willa Fitzgerald, Kyle Gallner, Madisen Beaty, Steven
Michael Quezada, Ed Begley Jr., and Barbara Hershey.
Set in rural Oregon, it follows a man (Gallner) and woman (Fitzgerald) who have a
one-night stand that devolves into a cat-and-mouse game of murder.
It is divided into six chapters in nonlinear order.
Principal photography began in Portland, Oregon on
August 22, 2022, and concluded on October 1.
The film marked the cinematographic debut of Giovanni Ribisi, who also
served as one of the producers, and was shot on 35 mm film.
Strange Darling premiered at Fantastic Fest on September 22, 2023, and was
theatrically released in the United States on August 23, 2024.
The film received positive reviews from critics, with particular praise
for the cinematography and the performances of the cast.
Despite this, it was a box office failure, grossing $4.8
million against its $4–10 million production budget.
The film explores themes of new york city, rape,
gore, sadomasochism, sexual violence.
The tone is intense and dark and mind_bending.